# Mojdeh Mansoori

Aarhus, Denmark.

**Mobile:** (+45)53336170

E-Mail: mojdeh.m@dent.au.dk



# Scientific profile

Having obtained my general dentistry qualification in 2012, I pursued advanced studies in the field of oral medicine specialization. Graduating as the top-ranked student in 2017, I subsequently practiced as a clinical professional until 2021. At present, I am deeply engaged as a Ph.D. student, dedicated to enhancing my research expertise and skills in the realm of orofacial pain.

# Educational and career background

## **Current position:**

March 2022 - present

Ph.D. student.

Name and location of institution: Section for orofacial pain and jaw function, department of dentistry and oral health, Aarhus University, Denmark

Project title: Epigenetic and nutritional risk factors for painful temporomandibular disorders.

#### **Clinical experiences:**

September 2017 – December 2021

Clinical practitioner.

During my employment at Bahonar Hospital, Kerman University of Medical Science in Kerman, Iran, I administered treatments to patients suffering oral mucosal diseases, orofacial pain, and temporomandibular disorders. Additionally, I contributed my expertise to Roshon dental clinic, a private practice located in Kerman.

#### **Postgraduate:**

September 2014 – August 2017

Residence of oral medicine.

Name and location of institution: Department of oral medicine and orofacial pain, dental school, Kerman University of Medical Sciences, Kerman, Iran.

Degree received: M.Sc.

Thesis title: Comparing the effect of chronic facial pain on tendency to morphine and cannabinoid in conditioned place preference in male rats.

### **Undergraduate:**

September 2006 – July 2012

General dentistry education.

Name and location of institution: Dental school, Kerman University of Medical

Sciences, Kerman, Iran. Degree received: DDS. Thesis title: Assessment of relationship between xerostomia and oral health-related quality of life in patients with rheumatoid arthritis.

#### **Honors and awards**

- Iranian Board of oral medicine, Iran, 2017
- Ranked 1st (top student), among all postgraduate students graduated in the same year (2017).

#### **Publications**

- 1. **Mansoori M.**, Exposto C.R., Bech B.H., Olsen S.F., Bjerregaard A.A., Diatchenko L., Baad-Hansen L., Adolescent dietary quality as a risk factor for painful TMD and headaches in young adults. (in preparation)
- 2. **Mansoori M.**, Zarei MR, Chamani G, Nazeri M., Mohamadi F., Alavi SS., Shabani M. Chronic migraine caused a higher rate of tendency to cannabinoid agonist compared to morphine: Tendency to use cannabis in chronic Migraine. Acta Bio Medica. 2020;91:e2020185. (published)
- 3. Navabi N, Zeynali M, **Mansori M**, Hashemipour MA, Nassab SA. Patients Attitudes' Toward Chairside Medical Screening in a Dental Setting. Pesquisa Brasileira em Odontopediatria e Clínica Integrada. 2020;20:4880. (published)
- 4. Raoof M, Soofiabadi S, Abbasnejad M, Kooshki R, Esmaeili-Mahani S, **Mansoori M**. Activation of orexin 1 receptors in the ventrolateral periaqueductal gray matter (vlPAG) modulates pulpal nociception and the induction of substance P in vlPAG and trigeminal nucleus caudalis. International endodontic journal. 2019;52:318-28. (published)
- 5. Chamani G, Shakibi MR, Zarei MR, Rad M, Pouyafard A, Parhizkar A, **Mansoori M.** Assessment of relationship between xerostomia and oral health-related quality of life in patients with rheumatoid arthritis. Oral Dis. 2017;23:1162-1167 (published)
- **6. Mansori M**, Mohseni-Rad L, Haghani J, Hashemipour MA. Dental students' opinions on the challenges and research opportunities: a qualitative research. Journal of Oral Health and Oral Epidemiology. 2017;7:8-15. (<a href="mailto:published">published</a>)
- 7. Tavakolinejad Z, Hashemipour MA, Shahravan A, Mirzadeh A, **Mansori M**, Gandjalikhan-Nassab SA. Evaluation of referral system to endodontists among a group of general dental practitioners. Journal of Oral Health and Oral Epidemiology. 2015;4:17-23. (published)
- 8. Hashemipour M, **Mansouri M**. Investigation of cases and referral patterns of patients to dental specialists by general dentists in 2011 in Kerman, Iran. Journal of Isfahan Dental School 2012;8: 433-443. (<u>published</u>)